

PROFILE

Driven Business IT student at his finish. Specialization in Software Engineering, with several projects e.g., in React Native and a Full-stack project with Signant Health as our client, Java, React, JavaScript, SQL, HTML, CSS, Git and GitHub. Provided with excellent communication- and teamworking skills.

CONTACT

+358 44 9847217

M

Buelent @hotmail.com

Helsinki, Finland

GitHub

https://github.com/Bulent2019

LANGUAGES



HOBBIES

Football Bouldering Photograph Music Chess

BÜLENT ARSLAN

Business IT Student

EDUCATION

Haag-Helia UAS

8/2019 - 2022 Business Information Technology, with specialization in Software Engineering.

HTL Secondary College for Engineering and Industrial Electronics

9/1995 - 3/2001

General qualification for university entrance, Obtain the electrical engineer, 2013.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Zara Finland Sales Assistant

09/2018 - ongoing

Customer service, teamwork, replenishment of stock, management of stockroom, delivery handling.

Light Insight KG Technician

01/12/2009 - 30/06/2017

Development and production of customized LED – Light Systems. Offer lapping, order purification and Calculation lapping.

Supplier management and warehouse logistics.

Manufacturing, processing, and analysis of printed circuit boards.

Test setup and power adaption of the light systems.

Calculating and dimensioning of light panels and technical documentation.

Customer advisor and technician on site.

Spectral analysis and quality testing.

SKILLS

